A Guide to the Tazewell family papers, 1623-1930
Library of Virginia
- 1 February 1799 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  John Ambler to Littleton Waller Tazewell, Kingsmill-offers condolences on death of his father
- 14 February 1799 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  John Beckley to Littleton Waller Tazewell, Kingsmill-enclosed some keys-papers will be sent with a congressman to Wickham in Richmond-clothes and other items sent to Nivison in Norfolk-states financial accounts-appreciates offer of a token of remembrance-again offers condolences
- 2 March 1799 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  John Beckley to Littleton Waller Tazewell-packet of letters being carried by Congressman Abraham Venable who will give them to John Wickham-clothes are being sent to Norfolk on ship "Little Jim"-Beckley and Mason on memorial and tombstone-sends some drafts and accounts-offers help in any way
- 29 March 1799 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  bond from Littleton Waller Tazewell and John Ambler to Benjamin C. Waller-concerning monies on the estate of Peyton Randolph
- 1 April 1799 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  Thomas Newton to William Diggs of Warwick County-estate of Colonel Tucker settled
- 8 April 1799 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  copy of will of Henry Tazewell dated 7 May 1797 proved in James City County Court
- 14 April 1799 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  John Beckley to Littleton Waller Tazewell-glad that keys and papers came to hand, that there was a will-tombstone-offers again to help if necessary
- May 1799 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  list of ships and cargo seized by French ships belonging to or underwritten by Thomas Whillock of Norfolk
- 2 May 1799 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  judicial record of York County Court-debt-Robert Thomas and George Nicolson against Peter Powell
- 27 May 1799 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  Philip Barraud-statement that settled account of Galt and Barraud against the estate of Henry Tazewell
- 30 May 1799 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  motion resolved to give adequate powers to high guard of Norfolk-regulations for appointment of fire wardens
- 7 June 1799 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  Robert Crew of London to John Nivison of Norfolk-disappointed in how a suit of his is being handled
- 10 June 1799 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  Moore Smith of Philadelphia to Benjamin Waller of Williamsburg-concerning a claim involving the United States
- 16 June 1799 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  Benjamin Waller of Williamsburg to Littleton Waller Tazewell of Richmond-enclosing the above-asks Tazewell to handle it before leaving Richmond
- 7 July 1799 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  John Beckley to Littleton Waller Tazewell-information about the tombstone including estimate
- 8 July 1799 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  account for a bottle of sherry wine from Robert Greenhow
- 19 July 1799 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  Robert H. Waller of Williamsburg to ?-nothing in law books on hand to help in a certain suit-discusses theories, common law and state law-asks if recipient could find some type of apprenticeship for a boy of a friend who recently died
- 21 August 1799 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  protest filed by Cleon Moore, notery public, for William Hartshorne and Sons--oversize box 13, folder 9
- 23 August 1799 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  answer of William Norvell of James City County to the bill of complaint filed by Mr. Bingley-sent to John Nivison
- 14 September 1799 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  from William White of Princess Anne County to John Nivison of Norfolk-concerning various legal papers
- 20 September 1799 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  John Beckley to Littleton Waller Tazewell-concerning father's tombstone-yellow fever is in Philadelphia delaying any kind of work
- October 1799 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  list of office judgments to October District Court-probably Williamsburg
- 30 October 1799 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  John Beckley to Littleton Waller Tazewell-concerned because had not received a reply to his last two letters (7 July, 15 September)-asks Tazewell to write
- 5 November 1799 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  John Beckley to Littleton Waller Tazewell--thanks him for writing--advises him to take care of his health
- 10 November 1799 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  Benjamin Taliaferro to Littleton Waller Tazewell asking Tazewell to loan him $120 so he can pay off a promissory note
- 18 December 1799 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  warrant for Thomas Ritson[?] in suit with George and Edward Ferry-for appearance in District Court in Suffolk
- [1800] (Box 2, Folder 6)
  complaint of John Hurte against Charles L. Beale for watch and chain that Hurte claims he lost and that Beale now has
- 10 January 1800 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  Commonwealth of Virginia to Baylor Hill and George Loyall to examine witnesses for a suit
- 11 January 1800 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  notice by George C. Lacy that he will be having depositions taken on 13 January for a suit brought against him by John Thompson
- 13 January 1800 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  depositions in Thompson vs. Lacy taken by George Loyall and Baylor Hill
- 11 February 1800 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  deposition of John Sinclair in a suit involving James Gordon and Robert Cairns of Glasgow and Johnston and McDowell of Norfolk, all merchants
- 17 March 1800 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  account of Miles King of Elizabeth City County with Littleton Waller Tazewell for legal services
- 17 March 1800 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  deed between John Wickham of Richmond, and Edward Carrington, Daniel Call, both of Richmond, and Littleton Waller Tazewell of Kingsmill-gives them shares in Bank of Baltimore to be held in trust-from estate of William Fanning
- 24 March 1800 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  agreement between John Hutchings and Aaron Cottle for repair of a vessel at Hutchings' expense
- 21 May 1800 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  John Beckley to Littleton Waller Tazewell-father's tombstone-possibility that Tazewell may be in Philadelphia
- 30 June 1800 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  statement of receipts by John Wickham of monies and etc. from the estate of William Fanning--oversize box 13, folder 9
- 27 August 1800 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  will of Denwood Smith of Somerset County Maryland-written 8 October 1798 and codicil 27 August 1800
- 11 December 1800 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  promissory note to refund to Richard Hurst $44 for brig if not brought to Hampton Roads
- 1801 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  sheet of paper with Augustine Moore's name on it
- 30 January 1801 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  receipt from John [?] to Francis Bright for Miles King
- 24 February 1801 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  will of Andrew Watson of Norfolk written 30 March 1798-recorded on 24 February 1801 in Norfolk Hustings court
- March 1801 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  Mr. Nivison's issue docket
- 25 March 1801 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  receipt for 1 gallon rum
- 28 March 1801 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  promissory note from Augustine Moore to Littleton Waller Tazewell for $5
- 10 May 1801 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  receipt from Benjamin Taliaferro to Littleton Waller Tazewell for 100 l due Taliaferro from the estate of Henry Tazewell
- 6 July 1801 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  unidentified account, last entry 6 July--oversize box 13, folder 9
- 22 July 1801 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  deed from Tristram and Eliza Butler to Matthew Butler, all of Norfolk County for 150 acres of land in St. Bride's Parish-acknowlegement of deed by Eliza Butler 23 July 1801-deed recorded 15 January 1802
- 24 July 1801 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  will of Benjamin Taliaferro of James City County-recorded 5 October 1801
- 13 August 1801 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  letter from Mary Fanning (his grandmother) concerning John Wickham's desire to settle the estate of William Fanning (her 2nd husband and father of Wickham's deceased wife)-concern over the poor health of Benjamin Taliaferro
- 15 August 1801 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  William Ludwell Lee to Littleton Waller Tazewell thanking Tazewell for an act of friendship that he can never forget-doesn't mention the act of friendship-sending 12 volumes of British statutes at large
- 12 September 1801 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  commission from Governor James Monroe appointing Littleton Waller Tazewell notary public for Norfolk
- 16 September 1801 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  account of George Jackson with Littleton Waller Tazewell-last entry is 16 September
- 19 September 1801 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  receipt to Benjamin Taliaferro for payment of tax on chariot
- 9 October 1801 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  receipt from John [?] to Francis Bright by an order on Miles King 24 l current money for bay mare and colt
- 6 November 1801 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  will of John Stratton
- 20 November 1801 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  Littleton Waller Tazewell account with Peter Powell
- 15 December 1801 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  promissory note for 60 l 19 s from Rebecca Taliaferro and William P. Harris to Littleton Waller Tazewell executor of estate of Benjamin Taliaferro
- 17 December 1801 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  John Harris of Richmond to Littleton Waller Tazewell at Kingsmill-money owed him by the late Benjamin Taliaferro
- 1802 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  Plat of Town Point in Norfolk (positive photostat)--oversize box 14, folder 14
- 1 January 1802 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  William Ludwell Lee of James City County to Littleton Waller Tazewell in Norfolk-concerning a lease involving Mr. Skipwith and Mrs. Paradise-mill is being improved, delay bringing a suit-paying a debt to Tazewell-asking Tazewell to handle a suit for him-sending venison along with the letter
- 28 January 1802 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  promissory note from Thomas Willock to Messrs. Soulage and Andre for $175
- 28 January 1802 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  receipt from William (?) Burney to Richard Hurst for $190 paid
- 31 January 1802 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  from William Ludwell Lee to Littleton Waller Tazewell-received letter from Tazewell-since Tazewell sure of invalidity of lease between Corbin and Skipwith asks that he institute an action-will relay a request to Major Allen-Lee not purchasing rum
- 8 February 1802 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  William Ludwell Lee to Littleton Waller Tazewell-Lee at Major Allen's (who apparently had bought Kingsmill from Tazewell)-valuing the furniture which Tazewell was selling to Allen
- 24 February 1802 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  William Ludwell Lee to Littleton Waller Tazewell-asking Tazewell to forward letters-asking about a deed for his 3 shares of Dismal Swamp Canal Company-Company said it was sent-Lee never received---asks what does he do if it is lost-hopes to see Tazewell at March Court in James City County-asks if process is issued against Skipwith-if so, please send and Lee'll take care of it
- 19 March 1802 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  agreement between Emanuel Jacomi of Norfolk County and Thomas Guin of Princess Anne County-Thomas Guin will purchase 63 1/3 acres on Broad Creek-installment of payments
- 30 March 1802 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  receipt from J. Williamson to Richard Hurst for $6 for payment
- 4 April 1802 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  William Ludwell Lee to Littleton Waller Tazewell-sending Tazewell money he owes for Tazewell paying a fee for him-invites Tazewell for a visit next time he's in James City County
- 26 April 1802 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  John Nivison of Norfolk to Governor James Monroe-actions of 54th Regiment during potential insurrection by blacks-detailed a guard to patrol at night-according to the mayor, free black had stated would have money out of bank and blacks out of jail-2 slaves convicted and sentenced to die, 2 others likely receive same-Nivison defends actions since insurrection not actual as stated in VA statutes-acted to protect city and inhabitants from potential insurrection-should've informed Governor earlier, but brigade general said he'd already written
- 2 May 1802 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  judicial record, James City County-debt Josias Moody against Littleton Waller Tazewell, executor of Benjamin Taliaferro-Moody is owed 58 l 8 s 8 p-discharged by payment of 29 l 4 s 4 p-interest and costs
- 2 May 1802 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  William Ludwell Lee to Littleton Waller Tazewell regarding his case against Moody-sends a fee, puts case into his hands-also reminds Tazewell of ejectment against Skipwith
- 16 May 1802 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  John Calvert of Norfolk to Littleton Waller Tazewell (in Suffolk at the time) regarding survey lands involved in suits involving Calvert-recommends having the land surveyed
- 19 May 1802 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  District Court in Accomack-William Ronald's admr vs John L. Fulwell's admr-judgment for 328 l 7 s 5 p
- 20 May 1802 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  receipt from William Wright to Francis Lynch for 21 l 14 s
- 21 May 1802 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  indenture between Prince "a Negro boy" and William J. Richardson, both of Norfolk, for Prince to serve aboard ship as an apprentice
- 27 May 1802 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  answer of William King of Norfolk County in response to bill of complaint brought by Robert Milton exr of Edward Hareford-admits having Peter a slave who had been purchased by Milton-states that Milton had wanted to buy slaves but that John Nivison had not sold slaves to him
- 19 June 1802 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  commission from Governor James Monroe to Littleton Waller Tazewell appointing him 2nd lieutenant of a cavalry troop in the 4th regiment, 4th division
- 21 August 1802 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  receipt from William Wright to Mr. Lynch for payment of 21 l 5 s for quarter rent
- 10 September 1802 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  promissory note from John Cowper and company to James Hawat and Compnay $1557.64
- 20 September 1802 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  invoice W. Burney to Mr. Bayley asking him to pay Rosemary for 6 days' work aboard the sloop Betsey
- 31 October 1802 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  William Ludwell Lee to Littleton Waller Tazewell-asks for copy of subpoena in a case so that Lee can send it to sheriff
- 1 November 1802 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  agreement with Christ Church Norfolk and John Nivison to rent pew number 26
- 6 November 1802 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  Littleton Waller Tazewell's account for clothes with William Richard-receipt that it is paid
- 18 November 1802 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  John Nivison as notary public filing a protest against maker of a promissory note from John Cowper and Company to John Howat and Company
- 21 November 1802 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  receipt from William Wright to Francis Lynch for payment of 21 l 4 s for a quarter rent
- 1 December 1802 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  Cyrus Griffin of Williamsburg to Littleton Waller Tazewell--replying to a letter from Tazewell--how an out of state creditor can get his money from an estate for debts owed
- 5 December 1802 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  survey for John Nivison along Main Street
- 8 December 1802 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  note from William Ludwell Lee stating he is sending a quarter of venison
- 1 January 1803 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  bond from Joseph Barlett to Littleton Waller Tazewell executor of Benjamin Taliaferro for hire of a slave named Charles
- 22 January 1803 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  John Wickham of Richmond to Littleton Waller Tazewell-concerning some bonds of Wickham's in Tazewell's possession
- 31 January 1803 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  John Wickham to Littleton Waller Tazewell-personal business
- 10 February 1803 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  Benjamin Waller of Williamsburg to Littleton Waller-Cato has brought the horses-glad that Tazewell and his brother-in-law had a good trip-mentions bill on the British government
- 11 February 1803 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  Benjamin Waller of Williamsburg to Littleton Waller Tazewell -death of William Ludwell Lee-left Tazewell his chariot, horses and made him an executor
- 24 February 1803 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  receipt from William Wright to John Johnson for 21 l 5 s for quarter rent
- March 1803 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  Littleton Waller Tazewell account with William P. Harris
- 15 March 1803 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  Judicial records quarterly session court of James City County-John Ambler and William P. Harris exrs of William Wilkinson vs Littleton Waller Tazewell exr of Benjamin Taliaferro-defendant must pay 62 l 13 s
- 15 March 1803 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  William P. Harris agent for Lucy Ludwell Paradise against Littleton Waller Tazewell exr for Benjamin Taliaferro-owes 37 l 2 s
- 28 March 1803 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  Benjamin Waller to Littleton Waller Tazewell-glad to hear that Tazewell will soon be up-will accompany him back to Norfolk--glad to hear Mrs. Tazewell is well
- 28 March 1803 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  James City County Court-exrs of William Wilkinson vs Littleton Waller Tazewell exr of Benjamin Taliaferro-Tazewell must pay 12 l 11 s 3 p
- 29 March 1803 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  John Wickham of Richmond to John Nivison of Norfolk-has received receipt for half note for $500 and is now sending the rest
- 5 April 1803 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  draft of letter, sender and recipient unknown, concerning the estate of a Mr. Boreland and his administrator Mr. Gillies
- 6 April 1803 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  Quintin Hamilton of Hampton to Conway Whittle concerning a note of Mr. William Thompson which has been paid
- 10 April 1803 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  promissory note from William Ward to David Moore
- 2 May 1803 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  judgment in James City County Court-John Ambler and William Price Harris exrs of William Wilkinson vs Littleton Waller Tazewell exr of Benjamin Taliaferro-plaintiffs recover 44 l 16 s 5 p
- 2 May 1803 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  judgment in James City County Court-John Ambler and William Price Harris exrs of William Wilkinson vs Littleton Waller Tazewell exr of Benjamin Taliaferro-plaintiffs recover 42 l 16 s 5 p
- June 1803 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  John Duthey vs Robert E. Steed-judgment for plaintiff for $75, damages and cost
- 4 June 1803 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  William Lane of Mathews County to Alexander Love of Norfolk-is working to get the money to pay Love what he owes
- 8 June 1803 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  Cyrus Griffin of Williamsburg to Littleton Waller Tazewell-can't hold court at time Tazewell wants-other business
- 9 June 1803 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  deed between John and Ann Taylor of Norfolk, first part, Matthias Jones and Thomas Darden, second part, and James Riddick 3rd part, Jones, Darden, and Riddick all of Suffolk-Taylors sell Riddick lot in Norfolk
- 20 June 1803 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  William Stiles to John Johnson regarding a suit of ejectment against Stiles by Aminadab Seekright in Norfolk court-other side is the ejectment
- 23 June 1803 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  John Wickham of Richmond to Littleton Waller Tazewell-legal opinion
- 18 July 1803 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  account and receipt-William Gregory to Charles Davis for Davis cleaning his pistol
- 28 July 1803 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  Christopher Fry of Norfolk to Littleton Waller Tazewell-asks Tazewell to begin a suit for him
- 31 July 1803 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  Benjamin Waller to Littleton Waller Tazewell-bill of exchange-invitation to stay with him if up for August Court-urges Tazewell and wife to visit
- 4 August 1803 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  Benjamin Waller to Littleton Waller Tazewell-financial matters
- 8 August 1803 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  to Christopher Fry-from a New York merchant firm concerning goods purchased by a Norfolk firm
- 20 August 1803 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- 31 August 1803 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  William Wirt in Richmond to Littleton Waller Tazewell-received money sent-glad that Tazewell is sending his wife to the Eastern Shore, but unhappy that Tazewell will be staying in Norfolk during the Yellow Fever
- 16 (or 10) September 1803 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  Robert B. Taylor of Norfolk to Littleton Waller Tazewell currently in Northampton-setting a date for a case they are involved in-envies Tazewell being in Northampton during sick time
- 1803 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  accounts of John Nivison and Littleton Waller Tazewell as notary publics to Commonwealth of Virginia
- 1803 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  estate of William Wilkinson in account with William P. Harris, executor
- September 1803 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  judgment in Williamsburg District Court-for Thomas Dent and Company against Littleton Waller Tazewell, administrator of Benjamin Taliaferro-payment for 74 l 8 s 8 p
- 8 September 1803 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  William Wirt to Littleton Waller Tazewell--letter--oversize box 13, folder 10
- 11 September 1803 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  John Wickham of Richmond to Littleton Waller Tazewell-legal matters
- 12 September 1803 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  shipping bill for Beriah Foster with Captain Owens on the schooner Olive Branch out of Norfolk
- 1 October 1803 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  William Wirt to Littleton Waller Tazewell asking Tazewell to send his old docket and papers for Williamsburg District Court
- 4 October 1803 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  John Wickham of Richmond to Littleton Waller Tazewell-discussing going to Suffolk court
- 7 October 1803 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  John Wickham of Richmond to Littleton Waller Tazewell-received his of the 29th September with $30 for fee-regrets not answering sooner-regrets professional engagements prevent him from seeing Tazewell
- 17 October 1803 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  suit by John Duthie against Robert Steed dropped with Steed paying costs-Suffolk District Court
- 19 October 1803 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  account of the Commonwealth of Virginia with John Nivison
- 28 October 1803 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  complaint of Joseph Henderson against Stephen Harris for $545.64
- November 1803 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  Peter Martin pltf vs Robert E. Steed def. for battery dismissed at defendant's costs
- 10 November 1803 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  Benjamin (?) Treson (?) to John Nivison asking Nivison to collect the money owed to him by Mr. Christian from a suit
- 13 November 1803 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  Littleton Waller Tazewell in Norfolk to John Randolph in Congress-introduces the British minister Merry and wife-asks Randolph to comment on the current politics-had meant to avoid politics but upcoming presidential election drawing him in-asks for Randolph's opinions
- 16 November 1803 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  William Wirt in Richmond to Littleton Waller Tazewell-Thomas Nelson died-Wirt interested in his position-asks for Thomas M. Randolph's help-asks for Tazewell to write letters if he will-asks about lodgings-chides Tazewell for not letting him know if he's dead or alive-news of health-may send his daughter down
- 24 November 1803 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  William Wirt to Littleton Waller Tazewell-is ill, can't make journey down for Norfolk court yet-hopes to be there for second day-"scolds" Tazewell for not replying about finding a house
- 6 December 1803 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  deed from John Hamilton with power of attorney for James and Margaret McDowell of Glasgow, Scotland, to John Nivison for a lot in Norfolk-recorded 23 July 1804
- 6 December 1803 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  Bond of John Hamilton to John Nivison for $1666.66 for a lot in the borough of Norfolk
- 18 December 1803 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  John Stratton of Northampton County to Littleton Waller Tazewell-Stratton had given Tazewell's legal opinion to Isaac Nottingham-Nottingham's offer of reimbursement too low-says if Tazewell sends charge, Stratton will try to collect it-asks Tazewell to forward an enclosure to Wirt
- 29 December 1803 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  Littleton Waller Tazewell to John Randolph in Washington-concerning the slave trade-how to punish the violators of the law-Captains make money even if lose ship--American vessels meeting up with Spanish or Portuguese vessels-wants Randolph to work to strengthen the laws
- 1804 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  Peyton Southall of York County to Littleton Waller Tazewell-has suit in Richmond chancery court-depends on the deposition of a man named Francis De Ende-asks Tazewell to see if this man is alive and in Norfolk-congratulates Tazewell on election to House of Delegates
- 1804 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  Benjamin Pollard to Littleton Waller Tazewell-spoke with Bennett Armstrong who said that he would pay $2 an acre for the swampland conveyed to Tazwell-if Tazewell is interested in Armstrong's offer, Armstrong will be at the county court-can mention it to him
- 1804 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  William Pennock to Littleton Waller Tazewell-regarding money owed
- 5 January 1804 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  John Nivison of Norfolk to Littleton Waller Tazewell in Williamsburg-price of corn-shipping corn?
- 8 January 1804 (Box 2, Folder 10)